A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Remind me again. What exactly is your plan?
Finding Krona and the Professor.
Yeah, I get that part. What I want to know is how you plan to do it.
Like I told you before, I'm going to push my soul perception ability to the limit.
Okay.
I'll filter it down, so I'm only searching for Krona. I'm sure I'll find something that way.
Have you gone out of your mind? How the hell are you going to pull that off?
I know what I'm doing. Searching a wide spectrum would be next to impossible.
So instead, I'll narrow down my search. Even if he's far away, I'm sure I'll be able to find him.
I'm not convinced it'll work.
It'll work. I still know Krona's wavelength.
You've always got an answer for everything, don't you?
Okay. Now let's see if I can find his wavelength.
Ready, soul?
Oh, yeah.
Let's go, soul resonance!
See you next time...
I'm falling down to my shadow
息を潜めて
待っている Deadly night
Don't scare me 君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams yeah baby
怖い夢だとしても
Felible 君のために
星を砕ぎ 飾り付けた
Black paper
信じてくれたなら
When you're lost in your world
Forever with your soul
見上げれば輝く
月のように
Forever with mine
N agua
енной音
Forever car
小さく así
Over there.
Over there. It's this way.
Weakling Krona's determination. For you. For always being by my side.
Over there.
This way.
Were you hoping to make a grand entrance? Something heroic?
Oh.
I expected better from my own child.
It looks like that's all the work we need to do around here. Okay. Which way to the Kishin?
We're too far ahead of the rest of our forces, Black Star. Let's head back and regroup with the others.
That's not happening.
Huh?
Other people would only get in my way.
Besides turning tail and running for covers beneath someone of my superior talent.
You know.
Whatever you say.
Let's make sure we can do it.
We can do it.
It looks like that's all the work we need to do around here.
Okay.
Which way to the Kishin?
We're too far ahead of the rest of our forces, Black Star.
Let's head back and regroup with the others.
That's not happening.
Huh?
Other people would only get in my way.
Besides turning tail and running for covers beneath someone of my superior talent.
You know.
Whatever you say.
Let's make sure we do this right.
Academy orders were specific.
Baba Yaga Castle is located in a cave in the jungle.
The first thing we need to do is infiltrate the cave.
From there, we carefully make our way to the castle.
There will likely be ambushes set up along the way that we'll need to look out for.
That's the first phase.
Once we've made it into the castle, we'll wait for further instructions.
Make sense?
So, basically what you're trying to tell me is the Kishin is inside that castle?
Right.
That makes things simple enough.
Let's get going!
You're gonna have to run a lot faster than that!
You hurt my feelings.
Why are you looking at me like that, grown up?
So sad.
Lady Medusa, I'm...
Here to...
The goal we've worked toward together for so long is finally within sight.
At a time like this, how could you doubt your own mother?
Because you're easy to doubt, Medusa.
You can hardly blame Krona.
You just tried to kill him without so much as saying hello!
Oh my, you're one of the Academy's teachers, yes?
Not anymore, I'm afraid.
Unfortunately for you, I left the DWMA recently.
Which means that little deal you worked out with the Academy, it doesn't apply to me.
Oh, is that so?
I simply can't imagine what a former teacher would want with me.
I'm here to bring Stein back!
You should hear yourself talk, how amusing!
I don't see what's so funny!
You don't, poor dear?
It's just that you sounded so hopeless and pathetic, a pitiful abandoned woman.
Well, putting that aside, Death should be ashamed of himself.
First he fails to uphold his end of our bargain.
Then he sends a child to finish off his own mother.
If you're looking for sympathy, you won't get any from me!
You brought this down on yourself, Medusa!
So, Krona, the Academy sent you after me and you came.
But now that you're here, what will you do?
I'm curious, why did you volunteer to come?
I need to put an end to this.
But do you really understand what that means?
Before this is all over, you may have to kill your own mother.
This decision can't be easy for you to make.
There's no other way. I understand that now.
I run. That's all I know how to do.
I turn away from whatever seems too difficult.
Anything I can't deal with.
Like when I lied to you before?
And when Professor Stein went missing?
I should have taken responsibility.
I wish I could believe you.
But I can't, not yet.
It's not an easy thing to regain the trust of someone you've betrayed.
I won't be able to forgive you until we've found Stein.
Until we've brought him home again.
As Stein's partner, I don't trust you to save him on your own.
I can't be completely sure how you'd react once you reached Medusa's hideout.
Can you do it, Crona?
I have to.
Are you going to answer me, Crona?
I'm here to...
I'm here to help someone who's important to me.
Someone who's been there for me no matter what.
I'm here to... I'm here to stop you, Medusa.
How disappointing.
After all I've done, I expected better from you.
Are you sure you won't reconsider?
He's sure. Accept it.
This is hopeless, you know.
No matter what you try, the two of you don't have enough power to hurt me.
And there's no way Stein's ever coming back with you.
He has no reason to leave me, you see. He's here of his own free will.
Liar!
Careful, you're beginning to sound pitiful again.
I won't let you get to me.
I know what you are. You're poison!
Every word from your mouth is a lie!
I'm not lying about this.
You can give yourself all the empty reassurances you want.
But the fact remains that Stein is never coming back to you.
He's all mine now, body and soul.
What makes you think you have the right to tear him away from me?
What are you to Stein, anyway?
This is making me sick!
You've said enough, now shut up!
I'm sure there's no need to remind you, but any damage you inflict on this body won't hurt just me.
Rachel will also suffer any pain.
Is there any low you won't sink to?
Let's recap the situation.
You can't do anything that would cause me physical harm.
Because that would mean injuring an innocent little girl as well.
Well...
Of course I can still hurt you.
Something tells me I'll enjoy this more than you will.
A little bit.
What am I supposed to do if the Academy brings the battle all the way into the castle?
Mizunez!
Right. Everything on Free's end is still the same.
I understand. Let me know if there are any changes.
Medusa gets to watch all this from the comfort of her home.
I'll never forgive her if she's taking a nap while I'm here dealing with this.
Now, would you like to get started?
Ready when you are?
We're eager to end this, too.
Why the face?
Not so confident now, are you?
You're confused, aren't you?
How can I be acting so calm and collected?
You're also asking yourself why, of all people, Krona and I were the ones sent here. Isn't that right?
No need to be coy. If you have something to say, say it.
See? You really want to know, don't you?
Oh, alright.
You're bluffing. What can you possibly hope to accomplish without a partner to help you?
You just don't get it, do you? You're fighting a Death Sidesmith!
The former Death Sides, didn't you quit?
Let's do this, Krona.
Right.
Very well. I can toy with you for a bit.
Are you sure you want to do this? I don't think it's a good idea!
What other choice do we have? I made my decision, it hasn't changed.
There are gonna be consequences!
Yes, I know that.
Vector Arrow!
Nice try!
How about a vector plate?
What's she doing?
What was that light?
The way he's moving, he's not fighting for real.
He isn't trying to hurt me.
Which means they must have some other strategy.
Vector Arrow!
It's not too late to stop this, Krona.
I'm tired of hating myself all the time.
And I'm tired of betraying the people I care about.
Most of all, I'm tired of being some tool for you to use.
Poor Krona.
Do you even know what you're saying?
You'll always be mine, nothing can change that.
No, no, you're wrong!
You're really still a good little kid, aren't you?
I'm not!
Your whole life you've listened to what I said.
You would do anything I told you to do.
Because I've always been the only one who was there for you.
That's different now.
Why bother denying the obvious?
You would never betray me.
How could you?
After all...
No matter what's happening...
You're still my child.
I don't care!
Child or not...
I have no choice but to kill you!
I've given you so much over the years, yet you still want to see me dead.
But that's not going to happen.
No, I'm afraid I can't let you kill me just yet.
We're about to see the dawn of a new world and I have no intention of missing that.
So, how about this?
I'll go ahead and kill you instead.
Medusa!
Vector Arrow!
Stay out of it.
You really shouldn't meddle in other people's family issues.
Some family?
Besides, you have more pressing matters to deal with at the moment.
Like defeating you, for instance.
Stein!
Marie.
You know who I am? That means...
Why are you still alive?
Why are you here? You're supposed to be dead?
What are you talking about? What made you think I was dead?
Oh, I see.
I guess that must have been another one of my nightmares.
The delusions that come with the madness.
Attacking me from the inside out until all of my lofty ideals crumble into dust.
Stein!
Please, Marie.
Please get out of my sight.
I don't know how much longer I can keep myself from dissecting you.
No!
Be careful.
I wouldn't let that woman come any closer if I were you.
Who knows what she might be planning?
Oh.
I do know.
I know what she's capable of.
I'm familiar with the skills she possesses.
I've seen them.
I've seen them all.
Then let's take care of them together.
The New World Order demands it of us.
My handy vector blade.
It was a cute little rebellion while it lasted, Krona, but it's all over now.
Get back on your feet, idiot! If you die, so do I! I won't let that happen!
Don't let that happen!
This is what all that talk about killing me comes to in the end?
Of course, I knew you wouldn't deliver.
At least you provided me with some entertainment.
Where am I?
What path should I take?
Move ahead?
Join the new order that's waiting to be born?
Or turn back to the old world?
Am I still stable?
Or am I being consumed by the madness?
Is this the truth that I'm seeing?
Or the fabricated delusions of insanity?
Water ever flows from higher elevations down to lower ground.
More and more water collects in one place, forming a river.
So it is, too, with the lives of men.
Set in their ways, they hate the loss of the old order.
They fear change.
But...
What if it's better to fall from higher ground?
To join the new river?
Old or new, everything is controlled by the order.
But that's okay.
The only thing I need right now is...
To obey the new rules.
I'm begging you, Stein. Please, listen to me!
I can't. There's something else I need to do at the moment.
I'm going to cut you open now!
What happened to your defiance?
Throw it out!
Now, Ragnarok!
Go away!
I know what you just did.
You think hardening the black blood will make you safe?
So wrong.
Have you forgotten who you're dealing with?
I'm the one who made you what you are in the first place.
Wake up, moron!
This isn't good! Pull yourself together!
Go, bloody needle!
It didn't...
Oh, don't tell me you still haven't noticed.
Let me explain it to you.
You see, I hit you with my sole wavelength.
Which, in turn, has made your wavelength significantly less stable, thereby rendering you virtually helpless.
You can't even use bloody needle.
And you will temporarily be unable to harden your blood.
Which means it'll be very easy indeed for me to cut you into pieces.
See it now?
Now.
This is the end.
It's time you die!
You die!
Oh!
Medusa!
so
Thank you.
Watch it or I'll...
You'll what?
No!